http://www.crushingplants.com/en/privacy-policy

This website or its third party tools use cookies, which are necessary to its functioning and required to achieve the purposes illustrated in the cookie policy. If you want to know more or withdraw your consent to all or some of the cookies, please refer to the cookie policy. By closing this banner, scrolling this page, clicking a link or continuing to browse otherwise, you agree to the use of cookies.CloseCookie policy
You are here:  Home /Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Details
Published: 09 June 2015
Category: Privacy policy (en)
Hits: 20570
Print
Email
Cookie Policy completa - Privacy Policy semplificata - Privacy Policy estesa
Cookie Policy
Cookies consist of portions of code installed in the browser that assist the Owner in providing the service according to the purposes described. Some of the purposes for which the Cookies are installed may also require the User's consent.
Technical Cookies and Cookies serving aggregated statistical purposes
Activity strictly necessary for the functioning of the service
This Application uses Cookies to save the User's session and to carry out other activities that are strictly necessary for the operation of the same, for example in relation to the distribution of traffic.
Activity regarding the saving of preferences, optimization, and statistics
This Application uses Cookies to save browsing preferences and to optimize the User's browsing experience. Among these Cookies are, for example, those to set the language and the currency or for the management of first party statistics employed directly by the Owner of the site.
Other types of Cookies or third-party tools that might use them
Some of the services listed below collect statistics in aggregated form and may not require the consent of the User or may be managed directly by the Owner - depending on how they are described - without the help of third parties.
If any third party operated services are listed among the tools below, these may be used to track Users’ browsing habits – in addition to the information specified herein and without the Owner’s knowledge. Please refer to the privacy policy of the listed services for detailed information:
Analytics
The services contained in this section enable the Owner to monitor and analyze web traffic and can be used to keep track of User behavior.
Google Analytics (Google Inc.)
Google Analytics is a web analysis service provided by Google Inc. (“Google”). Google utilizes the Data collected to track and examine the use of this Application, to prepare reports on its activities and share them with other Google services.Google may use the Data collected to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network.
Personal Data collected: Cookie and Usage data.
Place of processing : USA – Privacy Policy – Opt Out
Google AdWords conversion tracking (Google Inc.)
Google AdWords conversion tracking is an analytics service provided by Google Inc. that connects data from the Google AdWords advertising network with actions performed on this Application.
Personal Data collected: Cookie and Usage data.
Place of processing : USA – Privacy Policy
Contacting the User
Contact form (This Application)
By filling in the contact form with their Data, the User authorizes this Application to use these details to reply to requests for information, quotes or any other kind of request as indicated by the form’s header.
Personal Data collected: Address, Company name, Country, Email address, Fax number, First Name, Gender, Last Name, Phone number, Profession, Province, State, Various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service.
Mailing List or Newsletter (This Application)
By registering on the mailing list or for the newsletter, the User’s email address will be added to the contact list of those who may receive email messages containing information of commercial or promotional nature concerning this Application. Your email address might also be added to this list as a result of signing up to this Application or after making a purchase.
Personal Data collected: City, Cookie, Country, Email address, First Name, Gender, Last Name, Phone number, Profession, Province, State  Displaying content from external platforms
These services allow you to view content hosted on external platforms directly from the pages of this Application and interact with them.If a service of this kind is installed, it may still collect web traffic data for the pages where the service is installed, even when users do not use it.
Google Fonts (Google Inc.)
Google Fonts is a typeface visualization service provided by Google Inc. that allows this Application to incorporate content of this kind on its pages.
Personal Data collected: Cookie and Usage data.
Place of processing : USA – Privacy Policy
Vimeo video (Vimeo, LLC)
Vimeo is a video content visualization service provided by Vimeo, LLC that allows this Application to incorporate content of this kind on its pages.
Personal Data collected: Cookie and Usage data.
Place of processing : USA – Privacy Policy
Google Maps widget (Google Inc.)
Google Maps is a maps visualization service provided by Google Inc. that allows this Application to incorporate content of this kind on its pages.
Personal Data collected: Cookie and Usage data.
Place of processing : USA – Privacy Policy
Instagram widget (Instagram, Inc.)
Instagram is an image visualization service provided by Instagram, Inc. that allows this Application to incorporate content of this kind on its pages.
Personal Data collected: Cookie and Usage data.
Place of processing : USA – Privacy Policy
Issuu widget (Issuu, Inc)
Issuu is a digital content visualization service provided by Issuu, Inc. that allows this Application to incorporate content of this kind on its pages.
Personal Data collected: Cookie and Usage data.
Place of processing : USA – Privacy Policy
Youtube video widget (Google Inc.)
Youtube is a video content visualization service provided by Google Inc. that allows this Application to incorporate content of this kind on its pages.
Personal Data collected: Cookie and Usage data.
Place of processing : USA – Privacy Policy
Interaction with external social networks and platforms
These services allow interaction with social networks or other external platforms directly from the pages of this Application.The interaction and information obtained by this Application are always subject to the User’s privacy settings for each social network.If a service enabling interaction with social networks is installed it may still collect traffic data for the pages where the service is installed, even when Users do not use it.
Facebook Like button and social widgets (Facebook, Inc.)
The Facebook Like button and social widgets are services allowing interaction with the Facebook social network provided by Facebook, Inc.
Personal Data collected: Cookie and Usage data.
Place of processing : USA – Privacy Policy
Google+ +1 button and social widgets (Google Inc.)
The Google+ +1 button and social widgets are services allowing interaction with the Google+ social network provided by Google Inc.
Personal Data collected: Cookie and Usage data.
Place of processing : USA – Privacy Policy
Linkedin button and social widgets (LinkedIn Corporation)
The Linkedin button and social widgets are services allowing interaction with the Linkedin social network provided by LinkedIn Corporation.
Personal Data collected: Cookie and Usage data.
Place of processing : USA – Privacy Policy
Twitter Tweet button and social widgets (Twitter, Inc.)
The Twitter Tweet button and social widgets are services allowing interaction with the Twitter social network provided by Twitter, Inc.
Personal Data collected: Cookie and Usage data.
Place of processing : USA – Privacy Policy
Pinterest “Pin it” button and social widgets (Pinterest)
The Pinterest “Pin it” button and social widgets are services allowing interaction with the Pinterest platform provided by Pinterest Inc.
Personal Data collected: Cookie and Usage data.
Place of processing : USA – Privacy Policy
PAM protection
These services analyze the traffic of this Application, potentially containing Users' Personal Data, with the purpose of filtering it from parts of traffic, messages and content that are recognized as SPAM.
Google reCAPTCHA (Google Inc.)
Google reCAPTCHA is a SPAM protection service provided by Google Inc.
Personal Data collected: Cookie and Usage data.
Place of processing : USA – Privacy Policy
How can I manage the installation of Cookies?
In addition to what is specified in this document, the User can manage preferences for Cookies directly from within their own browser and prevent – for example – third parties from installing them. Through the browser preferences, it is also possible to delete Cookies installed in the past, including the Cookies that might possibly have saved the consent for the installation of Cookies by this website. It is important to note that by disabling all Cookies, the functioning of this site may be compromised. Users can find information about how to manage Cookies in their browser at the following addresses: Google Chrome, Mozilla Firefox, Apple Safari and Microsoft Windows Explorer.
In the case of services provided by third parties, Users can exercise their right to withdraw from the tracking activity by utilizing the information provided in the third party’s privacy policy, by clicking the opt-out link – if provided – or by contacting the third party.
Notwithstanding the above, the Owner informs that Users may take advantage of: Your Online Choices. This service allows Users to select their tracking preferences for most of the advertising tools. The Owner thus recommends that Users make use of this resource in addition to the information provided in this document.
Data Controller and Owner
Since the installation of third party Cookies and other tracking systems through the services used within this Application can not be technically controlled by the Owner, any specific references to Cookies and tracking systems installed by third parties are to be considered indicative. In order to obtain complete information, consult the privacy policy for the respective third party services listed in this document.
Given the objective complexity linked to the identification of technologies based on Cookies and their very close integration with the operation of the web, Users are encouraged to contact the Owner should they wish to receive any further information on the use of Cookies themselves and any possible use of them - for example, by a third party - carried out through this site.
Definitions and legal references:
Personal Data (or Data)
Any information regarding a natural person, a legal person, an institution or an association, which is, or can be, identified, even indirectly, by reference to any other information, including a personal identification number.
Usage Data
Information collected automatically from this Application (or third party services employed in this Application), which can include: the IP addresses or domain names of the computers utilized by the Users who use this Application, the URI addresses (Uniform Resource Identifier), the time of the request, the method utilized to submit the request to the server, the size of the file received in response, the numerical code indicating the status of the server's answer (successful outcome, error, etc.), the country of origin, the features of the browser and the operating system utilized by the User, the various time details per visit (e.g., the time spent on each page within the Application) and the details about the path followed within the Application with special reference to the sequence of pages visited, and other parameters about the device operating system and/or the User's IT environment.
User
The individual using this Application, which must coincide with or be authorized by the Data Subject, to whom the Personal Data refer.
Data Subject
The legal or natural person to whom the Personal Data refers.
Data Processor (or Data Supervisor)
The natural person, legal person, public administration or any other body, association or organization authorized by the Data Controller to process the Personal Data in compliance with this privacy policy.
Data Controller (or Owner)
The natural person, legal person, public administration or any other body, association or organization with the right, also jointly with another Data Controller, to make decisions regarding the purposes, and the methods of processing of Personal Data and the means used, including the security measures concerning the operation and use of this Application. The Data Controller, unless otherwise specified, is the Owner of this Application.
This Application
The hardware or software tool by which the Personal Data of the User is collected.
Cookie
Small piece of data stored in the User's device.
Legal information
Notice to European Users: this privacy statement has been prepared in fulfillment of the obligations under Art. 10 of EC Directive n. 95/46/EC, and under the provisions of Directive 2002/58/EC, as revised by Directive 2009/136/EC, on the subject of Cookies.
Simplified Privacy Policy
This Application collects some Personal Data from its Users.
Personal Data collected for the following purposes and using the following services:
Analytics
Google Analytics and Google AdWords conversion tracking
Personal Data: Cookie and Usage data
Contacting the User
Contact form
Personal Data: Address, Company name, Country, Date of Birth, Email address, Fax number, First Name, Gender, Last Name, Phone number, Profession, Province, State, Various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service, VAT Number and ZIP/Postal code
Mailing List or Newsletter
Personal Data: City, Cookie, Country, Email address, First Name, Gender, Last Name, Phone number, Profession, Province, State, Usage data and ZIP/Postal code
Displaying content from external platforms: Google Fonts, Vimeo video, Google Maps widget, Instagram widget, Issuu widget and Youtube video widget
Personal Data: Cookie and Usage data
Interaction with external social networks and platforms: Facebook Like button and social widgets, Google+ +1 button and social widgets, Linkedin button and social widgets, Twitter Tweet button and social widgets and Pinterest “Pin it” button and social widgets
Personal Data: Cookie and Usage data
SPAM protection:
Google reCAPTCHA
Personal Data: Cookie and Usage data
Contact information
Data owner
Machines Mobile Units Fixed Plants Cement Industry
Complete Privacy Policy
This Application collects some Personal Data from its Users.
Data Controller and Owner
Machines Mobile Units Fixed Plants Cement Industry
Types of Data collected
Among the types of Personal Data that this Application collects, by itself or through third parties, there are: First Name, Last Name, Gender, Phone number, VAT Number, Company name, Profession, Address, Fax number, Country, State, Province, Email address, Cookie, Usage data and City.
Other Personal Data collected may be described in other sections of this privacy policy or by dedicated explanation text contextually with the Data collection.The Personal Data may be freely provided by the User, or collected automatically when using this Application.Any use of Cookies - or of other tracking tools - by this Application or by the owners of third party services used by this Application, unless stated otherwise, serves to identify Users and remember their preferences, for the sole purpose of providing the service required by the User.Failure to provide certain Personal Data may make it impossible for this Application to provide its services.
Users are responsible for any Personal Data of third parties obtained, published or shared through this Application and confirm that they have the third party's consent to provide the Data to the Owner.
Mode and place of processing the Data
Methods of processing
The Data Controller processes the Data of Users in a proper manner and shall take appropriate security measures to prevent unauthorized access, disclosure, modification, or unauthorized destruction of the Data.The Data processing is carried out using computers and/or IT enabled tools, following organizational procedures and modes strictly related to the purposes indicated. In addition to the Data Controller, in some cases, the Data may be accessible to certain types of persons in charge, involved with the operation of the site (administration, sales, marketing, legal, system administration) or external parties (such as third party technical service providers, mail carriers, hosting providers, IT companies, communications agencies) appointed, if necessary, as Data Processors by the Owner. The updated list of these parties may be requested from the Data Controller at any time.
Place
The Data is processed at the Data Controller's operating offices and in any other places where the parties involved with the processing are located. For further information, please contact the Data Controller.
Retention time
The Data is kept for the time necessary to provide the service requested by the User, or stated by the purposes outlined in this document, and the User can always request that the Data Controller suspend or remove the data.
The use of the collected Data
The Data concerning the User is collected to allow the Owner to provide its services, as well as for the following purposes: Contacting the User, Analytics, Interaction with external social networks and platforms, Displaying content from external platforms and SPAM protection.
The Personal Data used for each purpose is outlined in the specific sections of this document.
Detailed information on the processing of Personal Data:
Personal Data is collected for the following purposes and using the following services:
Analytics
The services contained in this section enable the Owner to monitor and analyze web traffic and can be used to keep track of User behavior.
Google Analytics (Google Inc.)
Google Analytics is a web analysis service provided by Google Inc. (“Google”). Google utilizes the Data collected to track and examine the use of this Application, to prepare reports on its activities and share them with other Google services.Google may use the Data collected to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network.
Personal Data collected: Cookie and Usage data.
Place of processing : USA – Privacy Policy – Opt Out
Google AdWords conversion tracking (Google Inc.)
Google AdWords conversion tracking is an analytics service provided by Google Inc. that connects data from the Google AdWords advertising network with actions performed on this Application.
Personal Data collected: Cookie and Usage data.
Place of processing : USA – Privacy Policy
Displaying content from external platforms
These services allow you to view content hosted on external platforms directly from the pages of this Application and interact with them.If a service of this kind is installed, it may still collect web traffic data for the pages where the service is installed, even when users do not use it.
Google Fonts (Google Inc.)
Google Fonts is a typeface visualization service provided by Google Inc. that allows this Application to incorporate content of this kind on its pages.
Personal Data collected: Cookie and Usage data.
Place of processing : USA – Privacy Policy
Vimeo video (Vimeo, LLC)
Vimeo is a video content visualization service provided by Vimeo, LLC that allows this Application to incorporate content of this kind on its pages.
Personal Data collected: Cookie and Usage data.
Place of processing : USA – Privacy Policy
Google Maps widget (Google Inc.)
Google Maps is a maps visualization service provided by Google Inc. that allows this Application to incorporate content of this kind on its pages.
Personal Data collected: Cookie and Usage data.
Place of processing : USA – Privacy Policy
Instagram widget (Instagram, Inc.)
Instagram is an image visualization service provided by Instagram, Inc. that allows this Application to incorporate content of this kind on its pages.
Personal Data collected: Cookie and Usage data.
Place of processing : USA – Privacy Policy
Issuu widget (Issuu, Inc)
Issuu is a digital content visualization service provided by Issuu, Inc. that allows this Application to incorporate content of this kind on its pages.
Personal Data collected: Cookie and Usage data.
Place of processing : USA – Privacy Policy
Youtube video widget (Google Inc.)
Youtube is a video content visualization service provided by Google Inc. that allows this Application to incorporate content of this kind on its pages.
Personal Data collected: Cookie and Usage data.
Place of processing : USA – Privacy Policy
SPAM protection
These services analyze the traffic of this Application, potentially containing Users' Personal Data, with the purpose of filtering it from parts of traffic, messages and content that are recognized as SPAM.
Google reCAPTCHA (Google Inc.)
Google reCAPTCHA is a SPAM protection service provided by Google Inc.
Personal Data collected: Cookie and Usage data.
Place of processing : USA – Privacy Policy
Cookie Policy
This Application uses Cookies. To learn more and for a detailed cookie notice, you may consult the Cookie Policy.
Additional information about Data collection and processing
Legal action
The User's Personal Data may be used for legal purposes by the Data Controller, in Court or in the stages leading to possible legal action arising from improper use of this Application or the related services.The User declares to be aware that the Data Controller may be required to reveal personal data upon request of public authorities.
Additional information about User's Personal Data
In addition to the information contained in this privacy policy, this Application may provide the User with additional and contextual information concerning particular services or the collection and processing of Personal Data upon request.
System Logs and Maintenance
For operation and maintenance purposes, this Application and any third party services may collect files that record interaction with this Application (System Logs) or use for this purpose other Personal Data (such as IP Address).
Information not contained in this policy
More details concerning the collection or processing of Personal Data may be requested from the Data Controller at any time. Please see the contact information at the beginning of this document.
The rights of Users
Users have the right, at any time, to know whether their Personal Data has been stored and can consult the Data Controller to learn about their contents and origin, to verify their accuracy or to ask for them to be supplemented, cancelled, updated or corrected, or for their transformation into anonymous format or to block any data held in violation of the law, as well as to oppose their treatment for any and all legitimate reasons. Requests should be sent to the Data Controller at the contact information set out above.
This Application does not support “Do Not Track” requests.To determine whether any of the third party services it uses honor the “Do Not Track” requests, please read their privacy policies.
Changes to this privacy policy
The Data Controller reserves the right to make changes to this privacy policy at any time by giving notice to its Users on this page. It is strongly recommended to check this page often, referring to the date of the last modification listed at the bottom. If a User objects to any of the changes to the Policy, the User must cease using this Application and can request that the Data Controller removes the Personal Data. Unless stated otherwise, the then-current privacy policy applies to all Personal Data the Data Controller has about Users.
Information about this privacy policy
The Data Controller is responsible for this privacy policy, prepared starting from the modules provided by Iubenda and hosted on Iubenda's servers.
Definitions and legal references
Personal Data (or Data)
Any information regarding a natural person, a legal person, an institution or an association, which is, or can be, identified, even indirectly, by reference to any other information, including a personal identification number.
Usage Data
Information collected automatically from this Application (or third party services employed in this Application), which can include: the IP addresses or domain names of the computers utilized by the Users who use this Application, the URI addresses (Uniform Resource Identifier), the time of the request, the method utilized to submit the request to the server, the size of the file received in response, the numerical code indicating the status of the server's answer (successful outcome, error, etc.), the country of origin, the features of the browser and the operating system utilized by the User, the various time details per visit (e.g., the time spent on each page within the Application) and the details about the path followed within the Application with special reference to the sequence of pages visited, and other parameters about the device operating system and/or the User's IT environment.
User
The individual using this Application, which must coincide with or be authorized by the Data Subject, to whom the Personal Data refer.
Data Subject
The legal or natural person to whom the Personal Data refers.
Data Processor (or Data Supervisor)
The natural person, legal person, public administration or any other body, association or organization authorized by the Data Controller to process the Personal Data in compliance with this privacy policy.
Data Controller (or Owner)
The natural person, legal person, public administration or any other body, association or organization with the right, also jointly with another Data Controller, to make decisions regarding the purposes, and the methods of processing of Personal Data and the means used, including the security measures concerning the operation and use of this Application. The Data Controller, unless otherwise specified, is the Owner of this Application.
This Application
The hardware or software tool by which the Personal Data of the User is collected.
Cookie
Small piece of data stored in the User's device.
Legal information
Notice to European Users: this privacy statement has been prepared in fulfillment of the obligations under Art. 10 of EC Directive n. 95/46/EC, and under the provisions of Directive 2002/58/EC, as revised by Directive 2009/136/EC, on the subject of Cookies.
This privacy policy relates solely to this Application.
DOWNLOAD BROCHURE
Download manual
Reserved for Crifi customers onlyIn order to download the manual, please fill in the form
I authorise the use of my personal data in compliance with Art. 13 Legislative Decree 196/03.
Powered by ChronoForms - ChronoEngine.com
C.R.I.F.I. S.r.l. Crushing Plant, Via S. Gervasio,4A 4B - 61037 Mondolfo (PU), Italy – tel (+39) 0721-959931 - fax (+39) 0721-957132
Capitale Sociale € 51.000,00 I.V. - C.F. /P. I.V.A. IT00469280416 Reg. Imp. (PS) n° 4498 Trib. (PS) - Iscr. REA (PS) n° 86371 - Privacy policy
cialis online
italia |
viagra online
